[{"answer": " Chastain Amphitheater ticket office.  Can I help you", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Yes, hi.  Id like to buy tickets for the Justin Timberlake concert on the fifteenth", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Chastain Amphitheater ticket office.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " OK.  Just one moment.  It looks like the tickets range from $45 to $250", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Yes, hi.  Id like to buy tickets for the Justin Timberlake concert on the fifteenth", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " What is the difference between the prices", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": " OK.  Just one moment.  It looks like the tickets range from $45 to $250", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " $250 is for seats in the first five rows;  $175 is for seats in section A", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What is the difference between the prices", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " All right.  I guess Ill have to buy a $45 ticket.  Im on a budget", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 26, "question": " $250 is for seats in the first five rows;  $175 is for seats in section A", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " OK.  Ill need your credit card information please  the type of card", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 27, "question": " All right.  I guess Ill have to buy a $45 ticket.  Im on a budget", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Its a visa, #256485497215, expiration 8/5/2010", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 34, "question": " OK.  Ill need your credit card information please  the type of card", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " So thats a visa, #256485497216, expiration 8/5/201", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Its a visa, #256485497215, expiration 8/5/2010", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " No, the last number of the credit card is 5", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " So thats a visa, #256485497216, expiration 8/5/201", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Sorry sir, my mistake.  OK, your ticket should arrive by mail at the addres", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 37, "question": " No, the last number of the credit card is 5", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " No, that was it", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Sorry sir, my mistake.  OK, your ticket should arrive by mail at the addres", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK, thank you sir.  Have a nice day", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No, that was it", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Thank you, bye", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 44, "question": " OK, thank you sir.  Have a nice day", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Hello", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Thank you, bye", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Gary, hey, its Wes", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Hello", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Hey.  Whats up", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Gary, hey, its Wes", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Guess what concert I just bought tickets for", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Hey.  Whats up", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " What", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Guess what concert I just bought tickets for", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Justin Timberlake", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 56, "question": " What", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " I didnt know he was on tour", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Justin Timberlake", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yes.  Hes playing at Chastain on the fifteenth.  You should get a ticket", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 58, "question": " I didnt know he was on tour", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Id love to, but I cant really spend any money right now.  Things are kind o", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yes.  Hes playing at Chastain on the fifteenth.  You should get a ticket", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Yeah, I understand.  I had to get the cheapest tickets, which were still 45 dollars", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Id love to, but I cant really spend any money right now.  Things are kind o", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Thats expensive", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yeah, I understand.  I had to get the cheapest tickets, which were still 45 dollars", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " I know.  But Justin has five songs on the charts right now, so I guess hes reall", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Thats expensive", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " True.  Did you know that Justin Timberlake is really just his stage name?  Hi", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I know.  But Justin has five songs on the charts right now, so I guess hes reall", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " What?  Are you sure about that", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 76, "question": " True.  Did you know that Justin Timberlake is really just his stage name?  Hi", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Thats what I read.  I dont think hed be so popular with a name like that.  He ha", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " What?  Are you sure about that", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thats pretty funny.  I love his music, no matter what his name is.  I cant wait fo", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thats what I read.  I dont think hed be so popular with a name like that.  He ha", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Maybe Ill ask my parents if I can borrow some money.  If they say yes, Ill buy ", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Thats pretty funny.  I love his music, no matter what his name is.  I cant wait fo", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " That would be cool.  Its always more fun to go to a concert with someone else", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Maybe Ill ask my parents if I can borrow some money.  If they say yes, Ill buy ", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Yeah, I never have as much fun by myself", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 90, "question": " That would be cool.  Its always more fun to go to a concert with someone else", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Well, let me know if you decide to go", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Yeah, I never have as much fun by myself", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " OK.  I will", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Well, let me know if you decide to go", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Ive got to go now.  Ive got to go get something to eat", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 93, "question": " OK.  I will", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Ill talk to you later", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Ive got to go now.  Ive got to go get something to eat", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "10-01", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Ill talk to you later", "qSentId": 94}]
